The Heavy Knight.
Heavy Knight
It is a class specialized in defense that
draws enemy attacks to protect allies.
But compared to other
defensive classes, it lacks versatility.
Its incredibly weak offensive abilities
make it difficult to level up.
As a result
As a result...
it's known as a truly
unfortunate defective class.
Episode 1\h\h\h\h\hElymas the Heavy Knight
Every time I've learned
or seen something...
I've always felt like
I already knew what it was.
Huh? I get the sense
I've seen this before.
Doppellusion!
Doppellusion
I'll show you what
a Master Swordsman can do!
Cold-As-Steel Cutter!
And today...
I was about to undertake
the vital Ritual of Divine Blessing
as heir to the Edvaughn family.
It's finally time.
I'm nervous, too.
He's so gallant.
There's that odd feeling of déjà vu again.
It's all right, Elymas.
You're my son.
Have faith in the God of the Sword.
Elymas Edvaughn.
I grant you the divine
blessing of a class.
Baptisma.
Baptisma
I recognize this.
Five years ago—no, before that...
Before I was even born...
I obsessively played an online
VR game called Magic World,
and this world is exactly like that!
It's hard to believe,
but I've been reincarnated.
With everything I know about the game,
I'm guaranteed happiness and success.
If that's the case,
I hope I get my favorite class.
That broken class said to be
the strongest in Magic World.
Elymas Edvaughn
Attack
Defense
Magic
Speed
Equipment
Skills
Class Heavy Knight
Elymas Edvaughn
Attack
Defense
Yes!
I did it, Father! I'm a Heavy Knight!
Wh-What...
Father?
What did you just say?!
Master Swordsman, yes?
That's what you said, yes?!
What?
I mixed up my memories
from my past and present!
In this world, simple and powerful
classes are celebrated,
while technical classes that take time
to blossom are regarded poorly.
Their analysis and testing of classes
must be lagging behind.
Actually, um...
Show me.
Heavy Knight? What's the meaning of this?!
With low stats across the board
and no decent attack skills, it's useless!
Without a doubt, it's a defective class!
Father, please calm down.
It has the highest HP and Defense.
I don't care about that!
I'm glad this happened here.
The Edvaughns would be ruined if
we'd been publicly embarrassed like this.
I almost didn't recognize her.
She's so beautiful now.
Who is she?
She's beautiful.
She's from a branch family.
The daughter of a branch family, huh?
I'm supposed to undergo the
Ritual of Divine Blessing as well. May I?
Who does she think she is?
She should know her place.
She's the daughter
of an Edvaughn branch family.
Her name is Malice.
We played together
a few times as children,
but in part due to her status, we've
hardly spoken in the last five years.
They grow up so fast.
She's so brazen.
B-But currently...
It's fine. Begin the ritual.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Baptisma.
Baptisma
Class: Master Swordsman
Malice Edvaughn
Master Swordsman, huh?
Sorry.
I seem to have taken all the skill.
My bad feeling came true.
A branch family's daughter acquiring
the Master Swordsman class
could worsen my father's
already terrible mood.
Splendid, Malice!
I knew you were a true Edvaughn.
Malice, as of today, you are my daughter.
You will be my heir.
He named a branch family girl his heir?
It's not as though it's without precedent.
Father, I always thought
that Lord Elymas... no.
That Elymas could not bear
the burden of being your heir.
What?
Begone, Elymas.
You disappointed me.
You are no longer my son!
A Heavy Knight is a stain
on the Edvaughns' reputation!
Leave this mansion at once!
It's the wise choice.
Lord Elymas...
It can't be helped.
He's adopting the branch family girl?
F-Father, surely you don't mean that!
Heavy Knight is a strong class!
I promise I'll bring honor to—
Silence!
This is exactly what you deserve!
Don't show your face here again!
Don't use the Edvaughn
family name outside these walls.
If you do, I'll have your head!
Father!
Clean this up.
My father refused to listen to me.
It's not much.
It's fine.
I'm sorry I couldn't do anything for you.
I was given a few coins and
kicked out of the mansion that day.
Thank you.
Lord Elymas?
Should we recruit party members?
Anyone will do, as long as
they're a fast offensive class.
How have you been?
I'm planning to take on
a promotion quest soon.
I've got some pull with the examiners.
Wow.
Lord Teal's second to none!
Today's the day!
Today, I'll do my very best!
Yeah!
Just don't get in the way.
I wish you could at least hunt normally.
My husband's great
in public, but at home...
That's just men.
My piece of shit father
put me through hell.
I lost my home, my family,
and my life, but...
I've still got Heavy Knight,
the strongest class.
That said...
This world's history, environment,
and even this city's name of Rondalm,
are nothing like the game.
I'll have to do some research.
First, I'll test my class and skills.
Display stats.
Elymas Edvaughn
Attack
Defense
Magic
If things have changed and Heavy Knight
isn't overpowered, I'm screwed.
Skill Tree: Heavy Knight
Skill Points Remaining
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Defense Booster
Beginner Swordsmanship
Skill Tree: Heavy Knight
Skill Points Remaining
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Defense Booster
Beginner Swordsmanship
Good. It's the same.
Skill Tree
The skill tree.
These allow a person to choose
which types of skills they want.
\h\hSkill Tree: Heavy Knight
Skill Points Remaining
\h\h\hOath of the Heavy Armor
\hDefense Booster
Beginner Swordsmanship
I currently have
five remaining skill points.
These are the initial bonus points
gained when acquiring a class.
\h\hSkill Tree: Heavy Knight
Skill Points Remaining
Oath of the Heavy Armor
After that, you gain one more per level.
It's no exaggeration to say how these are
assigned determines a person's fate.
There are two types of skills.
Fixed skills determined by class,
Fixed Skills
and those randomly assigned
at character creation.
Random Skills
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Defense Booster
Beginner Swordsmanship
Of these, Oath of the Heavy Armor
is the only fixed class skill tree.
HA HA HA HA HA
People called it the weakest
of the Heavy Knight skill trees.
It can be decently strong,
but it's hard to use,
and many of its skills
have limited applications.
Defense Booster
is a pretty useful skill tree.
It doesn't grant any skills,
but it increases Defense.
Beginner
Swordsmanship
Beginner Swordsmanship isn't bad either.
When maxed out, it can be evolved
Advanced
Swordsmanship
into the Advanced Swordsmanship
skill tree with special items.
However...
Skill Tree: Heavy Knight
Skill Points Remaining
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Defense Booster
\hBeginner Swordsmanship
5 skill points assigned to Oath of the Heavy Knight
Oath of the Heavy Armor
has reached level 2.
Oath of the Heavy Armor has reached level 2
Rampart Reflection skill has been acquired
Rampart Reflection
skill has been acquired.
Oath of the Heavy Armor has reached level 5
Defense has increased by 10
Oath of the Heavy Armor
has reached level 5.
Defense has increased by 10.
All right.
This'll work.
Elymas Edvaughn
Attack
Defense
Magic
Speed
Equipment
Grunt Sword
Iron Armor
Skills
Rampart Reflection
A Raana, huh?
Display stats.
Monster:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRaana
Monster:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRaana
You don't waste time. Bring it on!
Rampart
Reflection
Rampart Reflection!
Level 2 reached.
Anyway...
Rampart Reflection skill.
This sure is gnarly.
Rampart Reflection
Common Skill
m 0 0 l 290 0 290 42 0 42
When an enemy melee attack is negated,
deal damage equal to the user's Defense
When an enemy attack
is negated by defense,
deal damage equal to the user's defense.
A level 2 Magic Stone.
It's not worth much,
but I'll hold onto it.
Help! Help me!
Th-They're going to kill me!
Are you an adventurer?
P-Please help me!
Let me handle this.
What?
Can you really take them?
Are you actually a famous
adventurer despite how you look?
No.
What?!
I just leveled up
for the first time in my life.
Y-You're hopeless!
You're way weaker than me!
A newbie can't handle that many monsters.
And take off that heavy armor!
We have to run!
Rampart Reflection isn't perfect.
Unless you negate all damage
with a defense vastly superior
to your opponent's attack,
it doesn't activate.
Run!
It's ineffective against superior
and unknown enemies.
But...
Come at me! Rampart Reflection!
What?!
Defense
I'm already familiar with starter enemies.
And I boosted my defense with
skill tree bonuses and equipment.
When it comes to fighting Raana...
I can beat dozens of them!
What?!
You beat that many Raana? Wh-Who are you?
I'm Elymas Edvau...
Don't use the Edvaughn family name
outside these walls.
If you do, I'll have your head!
Sorry.
No...
I'm Elymas the Heavy Knight.
I'm Elymas
the Heavy Knight.
I won my first battle as a Heavy Knight.
It's still the strongest class,
just like it was in the game.
But I need to level up to really shine.
I can't waste time here.
That's when a horrible monster
double my level appears before me.
Next time, "The Menacing Monkey Spider."
This battle isn't unwinnable!